Orefuwa Dominic

Front End Developer

CONTACT INFO:

Email: decryptus080@gmail.com LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/decryptus Portfolio: https://decryptus.vercel.app Github: https://github.com/Decryptus007/

SKILLS

- HTML and CSS
- CSS Frameworks (Bootsrap & Tailwind CSS)
- Git/Github
- JavaScript
- Rest API
- ReactJS
- Redux Toolkit
- Firebase

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

NATIONAL DIPLOMA IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

Kwara State Polytechnic | 2021-2022

- Graduated with a Upper Credit of 3.34
- Community advisor, Google Developer Student Clubs (GDSC)

CERTIFICATES:

- Completion of HTML course on Sololearn (https://www.sololearn.com/Certificate/1014-17844813/jpg/)
- Completion of CSS course on Sololearn (https://www.sololearn.com/Certificate/1023-17844813/jpg/)
- Completion of ReactJS course on Simplilearn (https://simpli.app.link/68vIQWZc8rb)

ABOUT ME

I am a skilled frontend developer with over 3 years of experience in building complex web applications. My expertise in modern frameworks, technologies, and design principles allows me to create visually appealing and intuitive user interfaces.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FRONT END DEVELOPER

OkadaNg | December 2022-Present

I was able to improve the platform's user interface by implementing an interactive google map that calculates the pickup and delivery location, which resulted in a 50% increase in user engagement.

FRONT END DEVELOPER

Awufbooking | September 2022-December 2022

Improved user engagement by 15% and mobile bookings by 20% through implementing mobile-responsive design and real-time booking system.

FRONT END DEVELOPER

FicHub | April 2019-July 2022

Increased student engagement by 25% by implementing a new user interface

PROJECTS

1. LOGISTICS COMPANY USER WEB APPLICATION (A CASE STUDY OF PACKIT LOGISTICS COMPANY)

- Researched and prototyped a scalable logististics web application UI after making over
 Surveys and data analytics from the survey team.
- To aid people in getting their packages delivered easily giving the user 100% satisfaction and reassurance.
 - Project aimed at decreasing the user stress level by 50% .
 - Enabling the users to deliver their product(s) at 1/2 of the conventional time.
 - Live Preview (User): https://pack-it.vercel.app

2. LOGISTICS COMPANY DRIVER WEB APPLICATION (A CASE STUDY OF PACKIT LOGISTICS COMPANY)

- Analyzed and built the driver user interface to interact with the user request after 100% confirmation from the project manager.
- Increasing communication by 100% between the driver and the user.
- Devised the web application using the same configuration used in building the (user) web application hereby making the production 30% faster.
 - Live Preview (Driver): https://packit-driver.vercel.app

3. WEB BASED MUSIC APPLICATION USING DEEZER RESTAPI

- Reasearched from 2 different sources and created a mini music player.
- Enable the user to quickly access to the top 100 trending musics.
- Live Preview: https://demuz-player.vercel.app

4. CAKE AND CONFECTIONARIES GALLERY WEB APP

- A case study of Empress Tee products which is acompany that specializes in baking and event planning having over 50 customer base.
 - A mini e-commerce web application that increases the product publicity by 25%
 - Helps the consumers of the product to get 5x access to products offered by the company.
 - Live Preview: https://empresstee.vercel.app/